Finding Aid for the Judy Kleinberg Papers LSC.1781
UCLA Library Special Collections
Judy Kleinberg papers
1982-2003
1983-1986
UCLA Library Special Collections
Kleinberg, Judy
LSC.1781
3.5 Linear Feet (5 boxes and 1 record carton)
Judy Kleinberg is an artist that appears to be mostly involved in the mail art scene. The collection consists of subject files and files pertaining to The 20 ANSWERS Mail Art Collaboration created by Kleinberg and Harry Warschauer in the early 1980s.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Judy Kleinberg, September 2004.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9971622373606533
Biography/History
There is very little biographical information available about Judy Kleinberg. Kleinberg is an artist that appears to be mostly involved in the mail art scene.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials relating to the career of artist Judy Kleinberg, specifically to mail art. Included are subject files and files pertaining to The 20 ANSWERS Mail Art Collaboration run by Kleinberg and Harry Warschauer in the early 1980s. The subject files consist of mail art specimens, personal correspondence, and a small amount of promotional flyers, address lists, and unsorted materials complied by Kleinberg. The 20 ANSWERS materials almost exclusively consist of mail art sent to Kleinberg or Warschauer.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series: Series 1. Subject Files; Series 2. 20 ANSWERS Mail Art Collaboration
Mail art -- Archives.; Kleinberg, Judy -- Archives
- Series 1: Subject Files, (1982-2003)
  Scope and Content
  The subject files reflect Kleinberg's participation and interest in the mail art scene. Among the files are one or more of the following: original mail art specimens such as postcards, envelopes and other paper works, personal correspondence to Kleinberg, promotional flyers and zines. The series is arranged alphabetically by last name of persons or groups. A small number of folders within the series are labeled Misc-Unsorted by the creator. They appear to be part of the subject files and are identified in the inventory as Unsorted.
  - Unsorted, (1984-1986) (Box 1)
  - Unsorted, (1984-1986) (Box 1)
  - Unsorted, (1984) (Box 1)
  - Unsorted, (1984-1986) (Box 1)
  - Unsorted, (1984-1986) (Box 1)
  - Unsorted, (1984-1986) (Box 2)
  - Unidentified Subject Files A-H, (1983-1986) (Box 5)
  - Unidentified Subject Files I-P, (1982-1985) (Box 5)
  - Unidentified Subject Files R, (1983-1984) (Box 5)
  - Unidentified Subject Files S-Z, (1983-1985) (Box 5)
  - Mail Art Specimen, (no date) (Box 6)
    Small plastic box with beads, paper, and other small items. Gives name and address of "Simonson."
  - Mail Art List, (1984-1986) (Box 2)
    Mail art address mailing lists, publications, and exhibition information.
  - Donn Alias, (no date) (Box 4)
  - Darlene Altschul, (1984) (Box 4)
  - Vittorio Baccelli, (1984-1985) (Box 4)
  - John M. Bennett, (1983-1984) (Box 4)
  - Guy Bleus, (1984) (Box 4)
  - Peggy Calvert, (1984) (Box 4)
  - Les Cammer, (1984-1987) (Box 4)
  - Ryosure Cohen, (1983-1990) (Box 4)
  - David Cole, (1984-1994) (Box 4)
    Bulk dates
    1984-1991
  - R. Comings, (1984) (Box 4)
  - Cracker Jack Kid, (1982-1984) (Box 4)
  - Peter Michael Craigie, (1984, no date) (Box 4)
  - Robin Crozier, (1984-2003) (Box 4)
  - Gene Elder, (no date) (Box 4)
  - Epistolary Stud Farm, (1982-1984) (Box 4)
  - John Evans, (1984-1985) (Box 4)
  - Arturo Fallico, (1982-1985) (Box 4)
  - James Ferine, (1982-1986, no date) (Box 6)
  - James Ferine, (1983) (Box 6)
    File entitled "Dancing Knutt (James Ferine)." Taken from cylinder mail enclosure addressed to Kleinberg from Ferine.
  - James Ferine, (1983) (Box 6)
    Cylinder mail enclosure addressed from Ferine to Kleinberg.
  - Pat Fish, (1982-1984) (Box 4)
  - Sue Fishbein, (1982-1986) (Box 4)
  - John Furnival, (1984-1985) (Box 4)
  - Gary Gach, (1985) (Box 4)
  - Ubaldo Giacomucci, (1984-1985) (Box 4)
  - David Greenberger, (1983-1986) (Box 4)
  - Hard Press, (1983) (Box 4)
  - Graf Haufen, (1986) (Box 4)
  - John Held Jr., (1984) (Box 4)
  - Scott Helmes, (1982-1984) (Box 4)
  - Horseman, (1984-1986) (Box 4)
  - Alex Igloo, (1983-1985) (Box 4)
  - John P. Jacob - HYPE, (1983-1985, no date) (Box 4)
  - Karl Kempton, (1982-1986) (Box 4)
  - Jurgen Kierspel, (1984-1985) (Box 4)
  - Bob Kirkman, (1985-1993) (Box 4)
  - Jim Klein, (1983-1984) (Box 4)
  - Kleinberg, (undated) (Box 4)
  - Chaw Mank, (1984, undated) (Box 4)
  - Tom Pack, (1983-1985, undated) (Box 4)
  - Jeffrey Peters, (1983-1984) (Box 4)
  - Runaway Pubs. James L. Berkman, (1980-1984) (Box 4)
  - Shannon Rund, (1985-1990) (Box 4)
  - Eric Solstein, (1982-1985) (Box 4)
  - TAM, (1984-1985, undated) (Box 4)
  - TUB, (1982-1991) (Box 4)
  - Richard Wanderman, (1983-1988, undated) (Box 3)
  - Harry Warschauer, (1983, undated) (Box 3)
  - Harry Warschauer, (1982-1984) (Box 4)
  - Harry Warschauer, (1983-1997) (Box 4)
    1984-1985.
  - Harry Warschauer, (1984-1997) (Box 4)
- Series 2: 20 ANSWERS Mail Art Collaboration, (1983-1984)
  The series consists of original mail art specimens addressed to Kleinberg and Warschauer and original flyer as part of the 20 ANSWERS Mail Art Collaboration from the early 1980s. There is no specific arrangement to the series and all files are labeled 20 ANSWERS.
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 2)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 2)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 2)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1983-1984) (Box 2)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 2)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 3)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 3)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 3)
    Original flyer, copies, and postcards that appear to be used to promote 20 ANSWERS.
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1984) (Box 3)
  - 20 ANSWERS, (1983-1984) (Box 3)